<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game>
		<path>./Millipede - Centipede.GB</path>
		<name>Arcade Classics 2: Centipede/Millipede</name>
		<desc>This is a compilation of two classic arcade games on one pak:
•Centipede
•Millipede</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Millipede - Centipede-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19950801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Accolade</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<playcount>5</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20141115T223019</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pang.GB</path>
		<name>Pang</name>
		<desc>Pang is a Puzzle game, developed and published by Ocean,  which was released in Europe in 1990.</desc>
		<developer>Ocean</developer>
		<genre> Puzzle</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./R-Type.GB</path>
		<name>R-Type</name>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/R-Type-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19910501T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bits Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Irem</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./R-Type 2.GB</path>
		<name>R-Type II</name>
		<desc>The game is the sequel to R-Type, which was first released as an arcade game in 1987 and profoundly influenced later shooting games with its charge shots, unique weaponry, and grotesque enemies. Hudson Soft ported the later 4 levels of the original R-Type to the TurboGrafx-16 with the title R-Type II, but the Hudson release is unrelated to the game described in this article.

The player controls a ship called the R-9C (or R-9 Custom), which is an improved version of its predecessor game's ship; the R-9. The ship's design was changed slightly, and the wave cannon was given homing capabilities. Two new types of weapons (the Search Laser and Shotgun Laser) were added, bringing the total number of weapon types up to five. A new anti-ground unit bomb was also added to the missile inventory.

Though the number of levels was decreased from the prequel, the number of enemies, their durability, and the number of bullets they shoot were greatly increased. Enemy movements and terrain were also made trickier, bringing the game's difficulty up considerably. The same revival system is used as in the prequel, where the player is brought back to a checkpoint whenever their ship is destroyed.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/R-Type 2-image.jpg</image>
		<developer></developer>
		<publisher></publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players></players>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20141115T220203</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario Land 1.GB</path>
		<name>Super Mario Land</name>
		<desc>The gameplay of Super Mario Land is similar to that of Super Mario Bros. and its Japanese successor for the Nintendo Entertainment System. As in the previous games, the player takes over the role of Mario. The ultimate objective is to defeat Tatanga, the "Mysterious Spaceman," and save Princess Daisy. However, there are some differences from earlier Mario games as well.

Mario's primary attack is to jump on top of his enemies, which normally kills them. However, there are a few antagonists who cannot be undone in this manner or may even cause damage to Mario if he jumps on them. Power-ups like the Super Mushroom work normally, but the Fire Flower enables Mario to throw "superballs" that fly at a 45-degree angle and ricochet off floors, walls, and ceilings. Unlike traditional fireballs, Superballs can also be used to collect coins, which is useful for coins that are difficult or impossible to reach otherwise. Also, unlike other games in the series, gameplay doesn't pause briefly when Mario collects a power-up or takes damage.

In two specific levels Mario flies in the "Sky Pop" aeroplane or travels in the "Marine Pop" submarine instead of walking. In these levels, there is no Super Flower because Mario can shoot the entire time. He still can grow by getting a Super Mushroom or become invincible by getting a Starman. During these levels, the screen constantly scrolls forward until it reaches the boss at the end, and it is not possible to slow down or stop it. Mario can be killed either by an enemy or by being crushed by the edge of the screen.

The game consists of four worlds with three levels each. At the end of every level, there is a tower with an access at the top and at the bottom. If Mario can reach the upper access, there is a bonus level in which the player can win extra lives or power-ups. If he only reaches the lower access, the game continues normally. At the end of every third level, Mario has to fight a boss by either battling it or getting around it to reach a point behind them that will end the battle, similar to fighting Bowser in the original Super Mario Bros. After the game is completed, the game returns to the title screen, and the player is given the option to play in "Hard Mode." If the game is finished in Hard Mode, the game goes back to the title screen and allows the player to choose which stage to start in, allowing for replay of any particular stage.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Mario Land 1-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19890421T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario Land 2 - 6 Golden Coins.GB</path>
		<name>Super Mario Land 2: 6 Golden Coins</name>
		<desc>The objective of Super Mario Land 2 is to reach the end of each level, defeating or avoiding enemies while doing so. The game retains several enemies from the Mario series, such as the Goomba and the Koopa, and also introduces several new enemies. Enemies can usually be defeated by jumping on their head, but also may need to be defeated in different ways, such as a fireball. Other famous mechanics include Warp Pipes, which allow the player to enter hidden areas or find shortcuts, coins, and ? Blocks, which hide coins and items. Unlike in previous Mario games, coins are not used to get lives; instead, they are used to play games in a special area that awards lives and other power-ups. To gain lives, instead, the player must find hearts like they did in the original. After killing 100 enemies, a star comes flying down which provides a short period of invincibility. The star can also be found at other places in the game. While being invincible, the 5th and each subsequent enemy killed will provide one life.

While its predecessor was similar to the original Super Mario Bros., Super Mario Land 2 has more in common with Super Mario Bros. 3 and Super Mario World: The player is no longer restricted to moving right in a level, and any level (except for the introductory stage) can be replayed. At the end of a level, there is a door that must be touched to clear a level. In addition, there is also a bell above the door which, if touched, activates a mini-game where the player can try to get either a power-up or extra lives.

There are 32 levels in total, based in several different themed zones. Some of the levels can only be accessed by entering in secret exits found in regular levels. Once the player clears or loses a life in these secret levels, he or she is returned to the level where the secret exit was found. Each zone has its own boss, which must be defeated to get one of the 6 Coins. If the player loses all of Mario's lives, all of the 6 Coins are returned to the bosses, which must be defeated again to retrieve the coins.

Super Mario Land 2 features three returning power-ups—the Super Mushroom, Fire Flower, and Starman. The Super Mushroom increases Mario's size, the Fire Flower gives him the ability to shoot fireballs, and the Starman makes Mario invincible to anything besides pits. Both the Super Mushroom and the Fire Flower also allow Mario to do a spin jump like in Super Mario World. Due to the grayscale palette, Fire Mario is differentiated from Super Mario by having a feather in his cap, a feature not seen in any other Mario series game. Also unique to Super Mario Land 2 is the Magic Carrot power-up, which turns Mario into Bunny Mario. Bunny Mario can jump higher, jump repeatedly by holding down the jump button, and descend slowly using his ear (Interestingly, this shows a similarity to the "Super Leaf" power-up in Super Mario Bros. 3).

Like Super Mario World, instead of going through a series of stages through each world, the player navigates a large overworld map that contains an additional map for each world with its own series of stages followed by a boss. However, the six worlds can be played in any order unlike in most Mario games that feature overworld maps. The game also saves the player's progress after beating a stage, though this is the first Mario game released to a portable console to have a save feature.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Mario Land 2 - 6 Golden Coins-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19921021T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario Land 3 - Wario Land.GB</path>
		<name>Wario Land: Super Mario Land 3</name>
		<desc>Wario Land: Super Mario Land 3 starts at the end of Super Mario Land 2: 6 Golden Coins. Wario Land features a theme of greed remarkably different from almost all of Nintendo's other franchises: It is the first game Nintendo has made where the main character's cause is decidedly selfish. There are no princesses to save, no world in peril. There is only one goal: for Wario to earn as much money as possible, in an effort to buy his own massive castle and make Mario jealous. The larger the cash total Wario has collected at the end of the game, the better house (and ending) that Wario will receive.

The Super Mario Land 3 subtitle links the game with the popular Super Mario Land 2. The game also increases its replay value by including a large hidden treasure chest in some levels. The chests (which can only be accessed by finding a special key placed elsewhere in the level) contain special one-of-a-kind treasures, which would each add a considerable amount to Wario's coin total at the end of the game.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gb/Mario Land 3 - Wario Land-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19940121T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
</gameList>
