<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario Pinball Land.gba</path>
		<name>Mario Pinball Land</name>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Mario Pinball Land-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20060615T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Fuse Games</developer>
		<publisher></publisher>
		<genre></genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Metroid Fusion.gba</path>
		<name>Metroid Fusion</name>
		<desc>Bounty hunter Samus Aran, the protagonist, explores the surface of the planet SR388 with a survey crew from Biologic Space Laboratories (BSL). She encounters an X Parasite, virions that can replicate their hosts' physical appearances and memories, killing them afterward. Samus is unknowingly infected by the virus, and proceeds to return to the BSL station, when she suddenly loses consciousness and is ejected from her ship before it crashes into a nearby asteroid belt. The Galactic Federation recovers her body and discovers that the X Parasite infected Samus's central nervous system. They counteract the parasite's damage by creating a vaccine using Samus's cellular sample from the remains of a Metroid that Samus previously contacted. The vaccine cures Samus and also gives her Metroid-like characteristics, including the ability to absorb and use the nuclei of X Parasites for nourishment, and the Metroid's vulnerability to extremely cold temperatures. Her infected Power Suit is sent to the BSL station for examination, although parts of the suit are bonded to her body and cannot be removed, forming a partially-armored suit known as the eponymous Fusion Suit. The Federation sends Samus to investigate an explosion aboard the BSL station. While there, she learns that the space station is swarming with organisms that are infected with X Parasites. A group of X Parasites manage to recover and use components of Samus's infected Power Suit to transform into the SA-X, a form of the parasite that partially mimics Samus at full power and possesses the Ice Beam that can exploit Samus's weakness to cold temperatures. Samus escapes from the SA-X before it attacks her, and continues exploring the space station. She discovers a restricted lab, which the Galactic Federation is secretly using to breed Metroids. Suddenly, the SA-X appears once again, and attempts to destroy the lab, with itself in it. Samus narrowly escapes the lab before it is destroyed, and later learns that the SA-X managed to asexually reproduce before perishing, subsequently cloning itself. In addition, Samus learns that the Galactic Federation plans to capture the X and the SA-X for further study. Samus is certain that the Federation underestimates the destructive power of the X Parasites, and takes it upon herself to destroy the BSL station by setting it on a collision course with SR388. As she prepares to exit the station, she encounters an Omega Metroid, which proceeds to destroy one of the SA-X. Samus absorbs the nucleus of the SA-X and uses her newly-restored Ice Beam to destroy the Omega Metroid, before escaping to her ship, which extracts her from the space station before it collides with SR388.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Metroid Fusion-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20021101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo Research &amp; Development 1</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./MetroidZero Mission.gba</path>
		<name>Metroid: Zero Mission</name>
		<desc>Space Pirates attack a Galactic Federation-owned space research vessel and seize samples of Metroid creatures. Dangerous floating organisms, Metroids can latch on to any organism and drain its life energy to kill it. The Space Pirates plan to replicate Metroids by exposing them to beta rays and then using them as biological weapons to destroy all living beings that oppose them. While searching for the stolen Metroids, the Galactic Federation locates the Space Pirates' base of operations on the planet Zebes. The Federation assaults the planet, but the Pirates resist, forcing the Federation to retreat. As a last resort, the Federation decides to send a lone bounty hunter to penetrate the Pirates' base and destroy Mother Brain, the mechanical life-form that controls the Space Pirates' fortress and its defenses. Considered the greatest of all bounty hunters, Samus Aran is chosen for the mission. Samus lands on the surface of Zebes and explores the planet, traveling through the planet's caverns. She eventually comes across Kraid, an ally of the Space Pirates, and Ridley, the Space Pirates' commander, and defeats them both. Along the way, Samus finds and destroys Mother Brain. However, while Samus leaves the planet in her gunship, it is attacked by Space Pirates, causing it to crash back on to Zebes, near the Space Pirate Mothership. Exploring the Mothership, Samus eventually reaches the Ridley Robot, a mechanized form of Ridley. After defeating it, Samus escapes the planet using one of the Space Pirate's shuttles, while the Mothership self-destructs.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/MetroidZero Mission-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20040209T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pac-Man Collection.gba</path>
		<name>Pac-Man Collection</name>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Pac-Man Collection-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20010712T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Mass Media</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players></players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20141115T212155</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pinball Advance.gba</path>
		<name>Pac-Man Pinball Advance</name>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Pinball Advance-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20050502T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Human Soft</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players></players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./R-Type III.gba</path>
		<name>R-Type III: The Third Lightning</name>
		<desc>R-Type III was originally released only on the Super NES, but later ported to the Game Boy Advance. The SNES version has been recently released for download at Virtual Console. It was the first game in the series to introduce new Forces. As well as the original Force (which was now named the Round Force, later named as the Standard Force in R-Type Delta), the player could choose from two other Forces: the Shadow Force and the Cyclone Force. These both had new, different weapon sets and special enhancements.
It also refined the weapons and charging system. It reverted to the original Red-Blue-Yellow weapon system, and the Diffusion Wave Cannon from R-Type II was replaced with a more standard wave cannon. Charging this cannon to full beam strength results in a massive, powerful beam that passes through all enemies and obstacles. A new weapon called the Hyper Wave Cannon was also added to the ship, which the player could use instead of the normal wave cannon if who desired. By switching to Hyper mode and supercharging the wave cannon, the ship temporarily gains the ability to use the Hyper Wave Cannon, which is unique among wave cannons in having a rapid fire capability. The shots fired create damaging explosions, and if the player has collected one or two Bits, they spin around the ship burning with energy. However, this Hyper mode causes the ship to overheat after a short while, and it must subsequently spend seconds cooling down, during which time the wave cannon is inoperative.
The fighter in R-Type III is identified in R-Type Final as the R-9Ø Ragnarök; it was originally referred to as 'R-90'. In fact, the original R-90 has been split into three in Final: the R-9S Strike Bomber has the R-90's basic Standard force unit and first wave cannon, identified as Mega Wave Cannon. Final's version of the R-90 has the Shadow Force and Hyper Wave Cannon, but is unable to choose its Force or switch between Wave Cannons. Finally, the R-9Ø2 Ragnarok II has the R-90's final Force, the Cyclone Force, and the Giga Wave Cannon, which can be charged through 7 loops. It can be assumed that this is because the original R-90 would simply be too powerful for the game to be any kind of challenge.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/R-Type III-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19931210T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Irem</developer>
		<publisher>DSI Games</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20141115T215855</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tetris Worlds.gba</path>
		<name>Tetris Worlds</name>
		<desc>For over a decade, the Tetris series has made an appearance on every game system. Tetris Worlds continues that streak, bringing their distinct brand of simple, yet addictive gameplay to the current generation of systems. Small shapes called Tetraminoes fall from the top of the screen to the bottom and you must rotate them and fit them together to complete lines. The game features six different variations of the classic Tetris, multiplayer mode for up to four players, and six different worlds. Sound easy? Once you start, you can't stop.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Tetris Worlds-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>20010905T000000</releasedate>
		<developer></developer>
		<publisher></publisher>
		<genre></genre>
		<players></players>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20141115T212514</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tomb Raider - The Prophecy.gba</path>
		<name>Tomb Raider: The Prophecy</name>
		<desc>Lara Croft discovers a manuscript which speaks of a mysterious occult magic which will bring desolation on earth in the near future. This prophecy also talks of three legendary stones which are linked with the mentioned devastation. Fascinated, Lara travels around the globe in search of these fabled stones. Along the way she'll meet enemies both human and otherwise and will also have to deal with dark magic of sorts.

Lara is now in a "quasi-3D" overhead environment, as opposed to the 2D-platformer view of the previous handheld (GBC) versions. This view proves helpful while Lara runs, jumps, shimmys, and shoots around. Although there is lack of a save feature, there is a password system which lets you restore back to 'almost' where you left.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Tomb Raider - The Prophecy-image.jpg</image>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20021112T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ubisoft</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20141115T212358</lastplayed>
	</game>
</gameList>
